<archimate:BusinessProcess
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="MSG-3 Analysis"
    id="1527bc75-1a6b-4dc2-8e86-c646851f58a8"
    documentation="MSG-3 analysis can start even if Design Office has not reach a high level of maturity.&#xD;&#xA;For MSG-3 analysis: extract of data from CorePDM and CATIA&#xD;&#xA;---&#xD;&#xA;From each analysis, MSG-3 generates the reports are validated by authorities (MRBR). Each report is&#xD;&#xA;reviewed. Up to 10 working group a year are organized to review 6 to 10 reports per working group.&#xD;&#xA;The required Input for these analysis:&#xD;&#xA;- VPM/CATIA: maturity required low ;&#xD;&#xA;- Describing document ;&#xD;&#xA;- Functional Hazard Analysis (FHA) based on indexes from Design Office: System Safety&#xD;&#xA;Assessment, FMECA, Reliability data&#xD;&#xA;- GSE&#xD;&#xA;- Testability analysis (BIT : Built In test &amp; HUMS)&#xD;&#xA;- SSI analysis require more mature DMU and BOM&#xD;&#xA;Workload : half a week to produce a report (~2man/week).&#xD;&#xA;Once reviewed by Airworthiness authority, the rework/update is about 10% of the activity.&#xD;&#xA;After each report is delivered, the MSG-3 consolidates the information to deliver a MRBR. The MRBR&#xD;&#xA;is delivered before EIS of the machine and is then updated once a year because of:&#xD;&#xA;- Product changes&#xD;&#xA;- New rules ;&#xD;&#xA;- Retex from operators.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;MRBR used by Tech Pub to produce the Master Servicing Manual. The MRBR delivery occurs ~9&#xD;&#xA;months before EIS.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;For each ECP, MSG-3 impact are analyzed: 5% of ECP imply a drastic impact on MSG-3 analysis. Note&#xD;&#xA;that 1 people is focused on impact analysis and 2 people to update the analysis and reports.&#xD;&#xA;The main pains are:&#xD;&#xA;- No described process for MSG-3 when H175 program started. The DOA is not updated. In the&#xD;&#xA;DOA it is mentioned that the DO shall run the MSG-3. Consequence at organization level.&#xD;&#xA;- No access to the data: 43% of time is spent to search for information from design office to&#xD;&#xA;perform MSG-3 analysis.&#xD;&#xA;- Difficult to commit on planning and budget.&#xD;&#xA;- The collaboration work with System Design Reponsible (DSR) depends upon the DSR (e.g.:&#xD;&#xA;lead-time to get the documents to be signed).&#xD;&#xA;- Maturity of information&#xD;&#xA;"/>
