<archimate:ApplicationFunction
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="(lae-F18) To manage users"
    id="da7a1c4e-65d2-4ff6-8b3f-cfbd9b243c57"
    documentation="Auto&#xD;&#xA;---&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-010&#x9;Users rights and access control&#x9;The system shall have built-in privilege (user rights) and access control capabilities sufficient to restrict individual users or defined groups (roles) of users access to data and/or transactions required for their specific work.&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-020&#x9;User identifications&#x9;The system shall be able to provide individual (nominative) user identifications.&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-030&#x9;Password rules&#x9;The system shall be able to enforce password rules (length, complexity, change cycle).&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-040&#x9;No Hard-coded passwords&#x9;The system shall not contain hard-coded passwords.&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-050&#x9;Passwords over the network&#x9;The system shall not transmit passwords in clear over the network.&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-060&#x9;Store passwords&#x9;The system shall not store passwords in clear.&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-070&#x9;Change initial passwords&#x9;Prior to entry into production, initial passwords for default/admin accounts as provided by the vendors must be changed according to password rules.&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-080&#x9;No Unauthenticated users&#x9;The system shall not allow “guest” or “anonymous” accounts (unauthenticated users). Such accounts must be disabled.&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-090&#x9;Security – logging and monitoring&#x9;The system shall provide logging and monitoring capabilities for successful and unsuccessful user log-on and log-off, and use of administrator privileges.&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-100&#x9;Anti-virus and patch management&#x9;The system shall be able to be included in anti-virus and patch management mechanisms.&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-110&#x9;Encrypted connections&#x9;It shall be ensured that any connection to other sites (or third party) is encrypted.&#xD;&#xA;R1&#x9;F18&#x9;BRD-SEC-120&#x9;Information assets control&#x9;All assets should be accounted for and have a nominal owner who’s responsible for it. Accountability should be assured. Assets include:&#xD;&#xA;· Data in databases and files, system documentation, manuals, training materials,…&#xD;&#xA;· Software&#xD;&#xA;· Computer and communication equipment, tapes, disks and auxiliary equipment.&#xD;&#xA;· Services   &#xD;&#xA;"/>
